is here with me my client an OFW for 13
years in Saudi Arabia sir Juan ah
he is going back to Saudi so let's interview him
now so we just finished the
transaction and then we will just ask
him something He is the plan that
you are getting with S maxel Prime So
what have you remembered the benefits on
that plan Yes I bought Sun Max
link Prime because I see the
um the advantage that there is
sunlight offered to me is great so
he has total disability He has a
fund called Prime
ah life insurance is really the main
benefit but he has an investment component
so he invested in stocks so
sir said is you can get something
you can expect fund value after a
period of time is it for retirement for
retirement on your own we know the
story of our life
yes yes yes i agree I only know
siran from my page because he inquired
So what made you trust me and Sun Life
I am an advisor or consultant of Sun Life
what I am looking at first is the
company I have been working with many
financial literates so they have the
sunlight  I have financial
training in seminars.
I have attended some. One of them is Sun
Life, the number one in the
Philippines when it comes to life insurance. I am a
diehard fan. So I thought
about Sun Life again. Yeah, and then
you haven't hesitated because you met
me, just on the
Facebook page. So it's not because at the
same time, I'm also asking
if the person is accredited or legit or
if he is certified or competent. So
that's okay. He passed the
consultant test. That's why I'm
thanking you. Thank you, sir Joan. And
lastly, sir, what
advice would you give to OFWs and the
financial side of my fellow OFWs?
We know that many of us are being
sent to the Philippines. Divide what
we earn, but let's put ourselves first. Let
's give ourselves
a reward. So that reward is
better. Church life insurance
and insurance because, as I said
earlier, in the near future, we will know
what will happen to us in terms of
working. Period of time reward too.
We
built a financial foundation. Yes,
not just for myself, but also for
my family. Thank you so much for
sharing your
stories. Bye, God bless everyone. Thank
you.